

#### About me



#### Nationality: Chinese



ShangHai Minxing District,China



kwang.xi915@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/wang-xi-6319b2235



+1419162741

### **Profile**



Senior software engineer with a bachelor's in computer science and 8+ years of experience in web development. Provide high-quality code and power communication.

Focused on creating collaborative efforts between support and engineering teams to implement system or product level changes to benefit end-users.

Eager to support building an impeccable online reputation by providing high-level customer support for startups and firms.

With in-depth knowledge of Artificial Intelligence, implemented deep learning to forecast Cryptocurrency price and made marketcompetitive tokens.

### **Skills**



- Rust
- Solidity
- Golang
- React&Redux
- Node
- Express
- Database
- Python&C/C++

## https://github.com/smartdev0530

#### Education

May 2012 - Sep 2015

City University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong

- Bachelor of Science (BS).
- · Gained extensive training.
- Academic Excellence in Computer Science, and English.
- Computer Science, Artificial Intelligence, Internet Security

## Work Experience

Mar 2021 - Feb 2022

PIRATES, INDIA

SENIOR SMART CONTRACT DEVELOPER

- Developed on-chain & off-chain governance protocol with MERCER-based tokens so that users are able to make decisions of adding new features and modifying current functionalities of the platform.
- Strategic and management consulting for blockchain and cryptocurrency, from ICOs to capital raises to systems design.
- Built and launched Smart Contracts for Genesis NFT, Pode and Marketplace as well. Prefer to use ERC-721 based NFT rather than ERC-1155
- Also built Staking Rewards contract, so investors earn MONA tokens by staking NFTs and LP tokens.
- Demystified Blockchain technology by offering Blockchain workshops and events.
- Worked on a BlockChain app that utilizes the Ethereum BlockChain for the creation of a supply chain management system interface using React.js.

May 2020 - Jan 2021

FRENCH PASS, LONDEN, ENGLAND SENIOR NFT DEVELOPER

- Developed whole smart contract from scratch and past the Audit from SlowMist.
- Implemented NFT fractionalization so that users are able to co-won NFT and decide further steps like sale, auction, airdrop together.
- Implement basic functionalities of NFT Marketplace such as sale, auction, airdrop and used proxy for service fee calculation.
- Worked on a POC for an automation reporting tool using all open source software utilizing ELK stack (Elasticsearch, Logstash and Kibana).
- Built web pages for customers using React.js, React native and Redux for responsive and highly reusable UX/UI system.

# value);

## **Work Experience**

Mar 20219 - Sep 2019

a MERN STACK APP FOR THE ELDERLY, SINGAPORE SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- Developed an E-commerce platform using React for frontend and NodeJS for backend.
- Developed Responsive Websites that could be served by desktop, Tablets and mobile devices using React.is.
- Integrated payment system for product checkout using Authorize, pet payment API.
- Worked with JEST unit test framework to write unit tests for JAVAScript code.
- Worked closely with the back-end team to display data using the Custom Components, library components, Redux, Redux-Saga.
- Worked with backend engineers to optimize existing API calls to create efficiencies by deprecating unneeded API calls.
- Involved in all agile ceremonies like Daily stand-ups, Backlog pointing sessions, Planning sessions, retrospection, etc.
- Implemented various screens for the frontend using React.js and used various predefined components from NPM(Node Package Manager) and redux library.
- Interacted with the Testing Team, Scrum Masters and Business Analysts to fix issues.

## Past projects

https://www.24northhotel.com

Developed an E-commerce platform using React for frontend and NodeJS for backend.

https://www.primekeeper.my

• Used React, particles.js, Google Cloud, React-Bootstrap, ...

https://www.hotel-amba.de

• Using Angular 4, Node, Express, .NET, Bootstrap, ...

https://oxfordcars.co.uk

- Migrated this platform from React to Vue.
- Used Vue 2.0, Vuex, Bootstrap, MySQL, Facebook API, Leaflet, ...

hhttps://jobeum.com

• Used Web3.js on Front-end,...

https://pegasus..to

- Migrated this platform from React to Vue.
- Used Vue 2.0, Vuex, Bootstrap, MySQL, Facebook API, Leaflet, ...